Hello, and welcome to Lesson 26 of this introduction to calculus with Wolfram U.
大家好，这里是 Wolfram U的微积分入门，第26课
The topic for this lesson is indefinite integrals.
本次课程的主题是  不定积分
Let’s begin with a brief overview of the lesson.
让我们从本课的简要概述开始
In the last lesson we talked about
上次我们说到
the fundamental theorem of calculus,
这个 微积分基本定理
which connects differential calculus and integral calculus.
它是 微分 和 积分 之间的一座桥梁
For example, if I said find the integral of this function, 4x^3,
例如，假如我说要算  4x^3 的积分
from 2 to 3, then the answer is simply 3^4  – 2^4—
在 2 到 3 之间它的积分 就是 3^4-2^4
that’s 65—
是65
and that’s because an antiderivative of 4x^3 is x^4.
这是因为 4x^3 的 原函数（也称 反导数 ） 是 x^4
Let’s just check that with D.
来让我们用 D 检查一下
If we try the same thing with Integrate
如果我们用积分干相同的事情
but now we tell it to find the integral of the function from 2 to 3,
但是 让他去算这个函数 2 到 3 之间的积分
you get back just the same answer.
得到的是相同的答案
What we’ve learned is that the antiderivative is, in fact,
我们刚学的这个 原函数， 事实上
a very nice way to do integration.
是非常好的算积分的一种方法
Hence, we give it a special name.
因此我们给它起个特殊的名字
We call it the indefinite integral.
我们称他为 不定积分
The goal of this lesson is to review the indefinite integrals
这次课我们的目标是复习 不定积分
or antiderivatives that you’ve learned so far.
或者说原函数，统统复习一遍
Before going on, just a few notes.
开始前，注意几点
First of all, to repeat myself,
首先，我再重复一遍
the antiderivative will now be referred to as the indefinite integral,
现在将反导数称为不定积分
and sometimes people just say integral.
有时候简称 积分
If you take Integrate and you find Integrate[f[x], x],
如果选择 积分，并且计算 Integrate[f[x], x]
then the answer is x^4 for our example
对我们的例子而言，答案是 x^4
because it’s really computing an indefinite integral
因为它实际上是在计算不定积分
when you do not give it any range.
当你不给它任何范围的时候
Notice one thing: that the answer from Integrate does not include
注意一件事：Integrate 的答案不包含
the constant of integration
积分常数
which you would learn in a course on calculus,
它是你在微积分课上会学到的
so you must put this in yourself.
所以得自己手动加
So please be careful when you work with indefinite integration.
所以请在计算 不定积分 的时候小心一点
You will need to put that constant in by hand.
你必须手动加上常数
Now if you want to compute a definite integral,
现在 我们要是计算 定积分
then you must actually put in the lower limit and the upper limit,
必须 输入 积分上限 和 积分下限
and then you get back the same answer you did earlier on,
然后很容易就得到先前的答案了
which is 65.
是 65
Here is a plot showing the function and its integral.
这个图画的的是这个函数和它的不定积分
Once again, please note that we’ll set the constant
重复一遍 注意！这里的积分常数
for the integral to be 0, essentially.
实际上在这个不定积分里 取的是 0
Let’s begin now with some examples.
现在我们再来点例子
If you take a constant function, then the integral of this function
对于一个  常值函数，它的不定积分
is just kx where k is the constant.
就是  kx， k 是那个常值
Again, mentally you must just put in the constant of integration,
再说一次，注意！ 必须要带积分常数
so you get kx + C.
所以 最终答案是 kx + C
For example, if the function is 3, then the integral is 3x.
例如，如果 函数是 常值 3，积分就是 3x
Here is a picture of the function and its integral.
这是函数和它的积分的图像
Notice that I am putting the Evaluate over here inside the plot,
注意我把 Evaluate 函数写在 Plot 函数内
and that’s because I’d like Integrate to do its work
是因为我希望先积分
before Plot does the plotting.
再令 Plot 函数进行绘图
Okay. On to a linear function.
好，那对于线性函数
Suppose you have kx + b
设其为 kx + b
Then its integral is kx^2/2 + bx + C.
那么积分就是 kx^2/2 + bx + C
That plus C, again, is coming from the constant in integration.
再说一遍，加的这个 C 是 积分常数
For example, if you have 5x + 4,  then the answer is (5x^2/2) + 4x.
例如对 5x + 4，答案是  (5x^2/2) + 4x
Here’s a plot of both the function and its integral.
这是函数及其积分的图像
Okay. On to power functions.
再看 幂函数
If you have x^a, then its integral is x^(a + 1)/(a + 1).
x^a 的 积分是  x^(a + 1)/(a + 1)
That’s the answer with the constant of integration.
这是带积分常数的答案。
For example, if I give you x^3, then the answer is x^4/4,
例如，x^3 的结果是 x^4/4
which you see in the plot over here.
图在这儿
Okay. On to trigonometric functions now.
再来看 三角函数
If you look at the sine function and the cosine function,
来看 sin x 和 cos x
then the integral of sine is negative cosine
sin x 的积分是  -cos x
because the derivative of negative cosine is sine.
因为 -cos x 的导数是 sin x
The integral of cosine is sine.
cos x 的积分是 sin x
So we have two important indefinite integrals
我们有了两个重要的 不定积分了
for sine and for cosine.
是关于 sin x 和 cos x 的
Here’s a plot of the functions and integrals.
函数和积分的图在这儿
Okay. On to slightly harder examples.
来看难一点的例子
If I give you secant times tangent
例如  sec x 乘 tan x
or negative cosecant times cotangent,
或者-csc x 乘 cot x
then in the first case, the integral is Sec[x]
第一个函数的积分是  Sec[x]
because the derivative of Sec[x] is Sec[x]Tan[x],
因为 Sec[x] 的导数是 Sec[x]Tan[x]
and similarly for the second example.
第二个例子也是如此
We’ve now found two more trig integrals.
现在我们发现了另外两个三角积分
Here’s a plot of all the functions involved over here.
这是涉及到的所有函数的图
As my final example, let’s take even harder trig functions.
最后一个例子，来看一个更难的三角函数
If I give you Sec[x]^2 and –Csc[x]^2,
我给你 Sec[x]^2 和 –Csc[x]^2
then the first integral is Tan[x]
第一个的积分是 Tan[x]
because the derivative of Tan[x] is Sec[x]^2,
因为 Tan[x]  的导数是 Sec[x]^2
and similarly, the derivative of Cot[x] is –Csc[x]^2.
同样，Cot[x] 的导数是 –Csc[x]^2
Again, here’s a plot of all the functions and their integrals.
这是函数和积分的图像
Okay. That’s all that there is for today’s lesson.
好，这是今天的课程的全部内容
It’s a short lesson where we’ve talked about
在今天的短课中我们讨论了
the antiderivative of a function and given it a special name,
函数的原函数并且给了它一个新名字
namely, the indefinite integral.
即 不定积分
What we have learned is that you can find
你会发现我们学到的是
the indefinite integrals of many functions—the constant function,
很多函数的不定积分——常函数
the linear function, the power function
线性函数和幂函数
and several trigonometric functions.
还有几个三角函数
Now in most cases you can simply call the Integrate function
在大多数情况下 只需调用 Integrate 函数
and it will find the indefinite integral for you,
它会计算出 不定积分
but make sure you put the constant of integration.
但是请确认，你加了积分常数
That’s really the core of indefinite integration.
那确实是不定积分的一个核心点
In the next lesson, we’ll talk about the substitution rule,
下节课我们讨论换元法
which actually makes things easier when you have
实际上能让你更容易地计算
more difficult examples
更难的例子
and perhaps more interesting examples to talk about.
也许会讨论一些更加有趣的例子
I’ll stop over here.
课程到此为止
Do review this very important lesson.
请务必复习这堂非常重要的课
It’s not very difficult, but it’s important
它不难，但是非常重要
and basically everything that follows,
它是一切的基础
and then the next time, we’ll talk about the substitution rule.
下节课我们将讨论换元法
Thank you very much. I’ll stop over here.
谢谢观看 本节课到此为止，再见
(翻译：周怀尚 兰州大学)
(校对：秦晋 北京师范大学)